Little Hana, the Elephant Calf
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
Once, my little canary pet, Piko was very agitated, so I checked our kitchen.
Then I realized that our stove had been leaking gas.
That must have been very dangerous!
it could have burst anytime!
Right. But thanks to our little Piko, our lives were saved.
Speaking of which, our dog Mook had once...
caught a robber who tried to sneak into our store..
Ain't that great?
Really?
My Mook is a very reliable dog.
Our Persian cat once retrieved my mum's lost ruby ring worth ¥1,000,000.
Animals are so loyal and lovely.
They love you back with interest added, if you love them.
True!
I'm leaving.
I too want an pet animal to catch robber and warn me about gas leakage.
I want to surprise all by buying an exquisite animal like a Lion or an Elephant.
Be reasonable!
You do know, your mum's hate for animals, don't you?
Yes, but...
I say, give it up!
But you'll surely come up with something, to help me.
Badger Robot from the future, Doraemon-kun!
You're flattering me!
Wild Pet House!
You can get animals using this?
Just wait and see for yourself!
There's a green plain over there!
Come on! Let's go!
Wow!
It's so vast!
Where are we?
It's an African Savanna.
It feels little like an Anywhere Door.
Yes, kinda...
It's a lion! Let's run!
We are saved!
I was so scared for life!
What are you saying now? You wanted to get a lion then.
Don't wanna! No need Lion anymore!
I wanna get some other animal.
If you turn the dial around, you may find the animal you prefer.
It's a Giraffe!
A Hippo.
I'm so disappointed.
An elephant.
That's it! An elephant!
Turn the dial around.
A Elephant calf! How cute!
Hope it's not abandoned.
Usually, elephant calves are surrounded by their mother and Elephants in their group.
Maybe they were shot by the poachers, and got lost.
I hope it's mother is okay.
This elephant calf isn't looking well.
It must be hungry, it needs milk.
Mum, gimme milk!
I managed to get a glass of milk.
I'll take care of that!
Big Light!
I knew you'd do something!
Drink up!
Why aren't you drinking?
Maybe it doesn't like a cow's milk!
No way!
It'll die if it doesn't drink it up.
I'll try feeding it the Momotaro Dumplings.
It's, for-all animal food.
It started drinking.
Aren't you happy, Young Elephant?
It's tickling me!
Come here, Little Hana!
Come on!
How cute!
Yay!
Are you still up, Nobita-kun?
You'll be late for school if you don't fall asleep now.
Say, Doraemon. I wonder how's Little Hana doing and what if it went somewhere else?
Don't worry, the door connects automatically to wherever Little Hana is.
It's Little Hana's scream!
It's a pack of Hyenas.
Even though it's an Elephant, it's but a baby, so it's still no mach for the pack of wolves...
Let's go home!
We are safe now.
Tonight let's sleep together!
Remember, we must send it back to Africa first thing, tomorrow morning...
Why not? Sure.
Little Hana!
Hey, Nobita!
You seem to be enjoying something!
Do you have some good news?
Cute Little Hana is waiting for me! I must go1
Wait for me, Little Hana!
Good boy!
Stop!
It's an herd of Elephants...
It must be the mother of Little Hana!
Let's run!
Hurry! Heave ho!
Say, Nobita-kun. We must return Little Hana to it's mother.
It can't be with you forever.
Japan is too packed and cold.
It might fall sick if we don't return it quickly...
It's best if we let Little Hana live with its mother...
in a vast, windy continent like Africa.
Nobita, run an errand for me!
Okay, mum.
Return Little Hana to Africa!
Stop.
Nobita, there's list of things to buy and money inside this bag.
What was that?
Nothing really.
Little Hana that Nobita-san got...
Why are you in such a hurry, Nobita?
Little Hana!
Little Hana is an Elephant?
Let's go and find out!
What's going on?
What's an elephant doing here?
No way!
Wait up, Little Hana!
Hey, stop!
Doraemon, take out your Bamboo 'Copter!
Go on, Little Hana.
Your mother is waiting for you!
Now, go!
Let's return home!